Ariunzul Ganbold (Jaga) Frontend Web Developer

Hello, you. Let me tell you a story.

A few months ago I went through a heartbreak. While I was going through the usual sad and crying stages of heartbreak, my cousin came to me and convinced me to learn to code. After doing some research on my own I sat in front of my computer to learn to code and haven't got up since then.

After starting to build my own website I was amazed how coding invoked my creative side and interest in creating and building something. And it quickly became one thing that keep me up all night, without coffee.

Since I learned how much I could do with coding, I have done my best to make coding my daily routine. I enrolled in Bloc Online Bootcamp and always search for ideas for my articles and challenge myself with learning a new thing every day. So keeping myself busy with new challenges, I was back to normal from the heartbreak.

With my new knowledge of coding, plus previous work experiences I believe I can be good value to any company and deliver a good work.

Thank you for taking the time to read my story.

Objective and Education

Objective Interested in a new experience and continuing	development of
--	----------------

programming skills and communication.

Education Bloc Online Bootcamp

2016

Front End Developer

Elgin Community College

Chicago, Illinois 2011-2013

Graphic Design

A + Nail School

Chicago, Illinois 2010-2011

Nail Technician

Manhattan High School

Manhattan, Kansas 2005-2006

MUS High School

Ulaanbaatar Mongolia 2004

Technical Skills HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Adobe Photoshop and Adobe

Illustrator

Ariunzul Ganbold (Jaga) Frontend Web Developer

Work Experience

Owner / Manager

Red 6 Nails

April 2013 - May 2016

After many years of experience in beauty industry, me and my two sisters opened the door for our own beauty salon in 2013. Our goal was to provide high-quality service in a sanitary environment that everyone can relax. With the responsibility as owner and manager, I expanded my experience in excellent customer service, handling appointments, training new employees, managing inventory and providing a workable environment for our employees.

Red 6 Nails client reviews...

"Love this hidden gem! The gold standard in nail care."

- Georgetta E.

"I have been coming here for a little over a year and LOVE this place. They just went through a remodel, and the place looks amazing. Nice environment, friendly people, and most importantly they do an excellent pedicure and manicure, as well as a great job keeping my eyebrows in check! They have some skills in nail art!"

- Mary L.

Work Experience Continued

Nail technician

Nail Bliss

March 2012 - March 2013

Blooming Nails

February 2010 - February 2012

With my new nail technician license in hand and with huge knowledge in mind I quickly entered the work field and started to build my own clientele by providing an excellent service and caring for each client with special care for their individual needs.

Server

Naomi Sushi

April 2006 - February 2010

My first job as a server I really believe it shaped me to be a good employee. By working in a very popular restaurant I earned an ability to work in a fast-paced environment, multitasking and being responsible for customers satisfaction. Soon I started to mentor and train new servers with knowledge of restaurant system and procedures.

Ariunzul Ganbold (Jaga) Frontend Web Developer

Contact Information

Phone 773.698.4554

Email jagamongol@gmail.com

URL jagamongol.com

Github jagamongol